Guide to the Lafayette Avenue Presbyterian Church records 2009.011
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 18: Photographs, 1890s-2002
  Please note that additional photographs can be found throughout the collection, and are typically filed with other documents which are thematically related. For instance, Sub-series 5.1: Rev. Theodore L. Cuyler includes numerous portraits of Rev. Cuyler, and photographs of the Underwood family can be found in Sub-series 13.2: Underwood family and Korean Congregation
  - 1890s-1910s photographs (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Group photograph of Elders, circa 1890s (Box 40, Folder -)
  - Photographs identified by Louise Cumberbatch, circa 1890s-1940s (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Lillian Conard Gosnell's photographs, circa 1900s-1930s (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Photograph album, 1928-1929 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - 1930s photographs (2 folders) (Box 29, Folder 19-20)
    Includes Boy Scouts, Girl Scouts, church club dramatic groups, Majorie Vetter, David Porter, Rev. Magary, Business Girls Supper Group, Anna L. Colcord, Wallace Dunbar Vincent, and others
  - Roll Call prints and negatives, 1933-1934 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    Includes Rev. Magary and others
  - John Ewing Steen framed photographs (Associate Pastor, 1926-1941), circa 1940s (Box 35, Folder -)
  - 1940s-1960s photographs, circa 1940s-1960s (Box 29, Folder 22)
    Includes Anna L. Colcord, Marjorie Vetter, Emma Jessie Ogg, an unidentified organist, and others
  - 1960s slides (Box 34, Folder -)
  - William Holden framed photograph (Treasurer), circa 1950s (Box 35, Folder -)
  - Lillian Conard Gosnell framed photograph (Clerk of Session, 1972-1989), circa 1970s-1980s (Box 35, Folder -)
  - Dedication of Cuyler Gore, 1970s (Box 29, Folder 23)
    Includes Rev. Knight and others
  - 1970s photographs (Box 29, Folder 24)
    Includes Summer Youth Program, Vivian Douglass, Rev. Knight, and others
  - 1980s photographs (2 folders) (Box 29, Folder 25-26)
    Includes dedication of Brooklyn Public Library's Clinton Hill branch
  - 1990s photographs (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Oliver and Dalmus photographs, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 10)